Giant lizards!
Komodo dragons...
Take her to the other side of the river.
R-Right...
I'll get the BIMs.
What?
That's crazy, Sakamoto-han!
Hey, hang in there...
Sakamoto-han, get back here!
What are you doing?
It isn't exploding!
Wh-Why?!
The switch isn't working!
I took these BIMs from that kid.
Maybe they don't count as my BIMs
because I didn't kill him or something?
Sakamoto-han!
Taira-san!
Which ones are mine?
N-Not these, either.
Damn it!
Stay back, damn it!
Stay back!
T-Taira-san!
This is a disaster...
My right leg again...
I'm sorry to make you carry everything.
It's fine.
We got everything in one trunk.
And you have it worse.
You've got it worse.
We need to stop the bleeding on that leg.
We don't have the time.
More importantly, be sure you
keep that girl on your back.
Right...
They're following us.
You're a real hero, Sakamoto-han.
Not many people like you around these days.
That isn't true.
Why didn't you run and leave us behind?
From your perspective,
we're just an old guy and
an unconscious girl you don't
even know, slowing you down.
In that situation, no one would
blame you if you'd left us to die.
Taira-san, why are you always
saying things like that?
Are you testing me?
I wonder why...
I don't know.
But I'm scared.
When you left to go fight,
I wondered if maybe you wouldn't come back,
if you had abandoned me...
It was all I could think about.
It terrified me.
What we talked about afterwards...
When that girl said
that someone wanted to get rid of us.
It seems to me that it might be true...
I was kind to my family,
but I was a monster at work.
I took advantage of loopholes
and gray areas in the law.
It wouldn't surprise me if
any of them hated me.
This is karma...
Anything you do wrong will come
back to you in the end.
Yes, this is my punishment.
I...
I won't betray you.
Th-They're close!
Run! Run!
Hey... Wait!
Taira-san!
Damn it.
Taira-san...
Taira-san!
Where did you go, Taira-san?
We got separated?
No, that isn't right.
If I can't see him with radar,
then he isn't moving.
Why wouldn't he move
at a time like this?
In that situation, no one would
blame you if you'd left us to die.
He has the food and her BIMs...
Maybe he left her with me,
while he made off with our supplies?
Have I been abandoned?
No way...
I can't believe it.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Screw you, you old bastard!
C-Crap!
Crap...
That BIM...
Sakamoto-han!
Are you okay?
I've been looking everywhere for you!
He didn't run?
We were both looking for each other.
So our radars canceled
each other out?
Taira-san, I doubted you...
I...
When you're scared, all you
can think is the worst.
I'm the same way.
So never give up hope!
Right?
Night of Sacrifice
Right...
But are you sure about this, Taira-san?
Weren't you keeping your
BIM type secret?
Sorry.
I still didn't trust you...
I didn't want to make enemies
or let anyone get close.
That's how I've lived.
But you risked your life for me.
You believed in me.
I was so happy.
"If I stay with this person, I'll be saved.
So I have to trust him completely."
That's all it was.
The sea breeze!
We're close to the sea.
Taira-san...
Look.
Sakamoto-han!
Hurry!
We've gotta climb this thing?
What about her?
We'll have to get her up there together.
Let's go!
Right, that's it...
You can do it.
You can do it...
I'll buy time.
You get the girl up there.
I can't do it alone.
That ladder's all rusted.
And his BIMs are a homing type.
They'll lock on,
then home in.
But they aren't very powerful.
Hey!
Climb up there on your own!
Please...
Please!
Wake up!
Karma...
Is this my punishment?
If we sacrifice her, we can survive.
But...
I can't do something so cruel.
You want me...
You want me to become a monster?
No!
This won't hold them off!
Sakamoto-han, are you up there yet?
Wh-What are you doing?
Is he insane?
Is he going to sacrifice her,
so he can survive?
I've lost faith in you.
I've lost faith in you, Sakamoto-han!
What's that smoke?
Get back, Taira-san.
That's the burning gas type BIM she had.
It's very toxic.
Her BIM?
Back there, you said you could
only use your own BIMs.
Yes, but I just had an idea.
I found another way.
I made her push the switch.
I didn't know that was possible...
But the gas is spreading.
There's nowhere to run.
It'll be fine.
As long as we're here.
Here, where the sea wind is blowing.
The sea wind?
The sea winds blow in here,
and we're surrounded by rocks.
Places like this are where the
burning gas type is most effective.
A-Amazing!
That's amazing, Sakamoto-han!
This game is different from BTOOOM!...
In BTOOOM!, there isn't any wind,
and you can't take and use
someone else's BIMs.
This is real BTOOOM!
in the real world.
Seems a BIM killed someone here.
That isn't recent.
Maybe there was a game like
this one before we arrived.
Tired...
Taira-san, are you okay?
Well, we'll be safe here.
You know, I was starting to
wonder what you were thinking
when you climbed the ladder alone.
M-Maybe it's because I can finally relax...
But I feel really dizzy.
Oh, no...
O-Ow! Ouch!
The leg that was bitten
just started hurting...
He has a bad fever!
Are the lizards gone?
Five of them are dead.
I'd bet the rest returned to the forest.
And it still smells like poison around here.
I doubt they'll be back.
What are you looking at?
Nothing. I wasn't looking.
Come to think of it,
you didn't do anything weird
while I was out, did you?
Weird?
Y-You did!
You pervert!
W-Wait.
I didn't do anything...
Shut up.
I can tell by your face!
Stay away from me, ass.
Don't jump to conclusions...
Don't...
Don't touch me!
S-Sorry.
Taira-san, are you okay?
Keep going!
Don't just stand there!
Help me!
We need to disinfect it.
Help me hold him down.
What are you doing?
Hurry!
No!
I don't want to touch any man!
What are you talking about?
This isn't the time for that!
He got bitten trying to protect you.
Hurry!
Okay, here we go!
What happens
to us now?
From now on...
Hey, there!
Good morning.
Thanks for the all-nighter!
Here are some snacks.
Thank you.
Well?
Anything good happen?
Nothing notable at the moment.
Oh, my...
Looks like Sakamoto-kun is still alive.
Yes.
He's already made contact
with four other players,
but he only killed the first one.
It appears he's gathering allies.
I see.
That sounds like him.
He'll give us some good data.
Make sure you collect it all.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Our First Cosplay
You won't get cell reception out here.
Wh-What are you doing?
Don't scare me like that.
I was just thinking that
we're working together,
but I don't know your name yet.
Was that picture from a photo booth?
So you do cosplay.
Is that character...
Don't look at my cell phone!
You pervert.
Wh-What are you doing?!
That's my line, you ass.
And I'm not working with you two.
I don't trust men, so there's no point
in giving you my name!
Whether you're working with us or not,
I want to ask you this.
All those BIMs and that food you have.
How did you get them?
You didn't have only that trunk.
You had crackers and timers,
and burning gas types, as well.
You can only use your own BIMs.
To use another player's BIMs,
you can't just steal them.
You have to kill the enemy player
before they'll belong to you.
How many have you killed?
Sakamoto-han, are you
saying she's a murderer?
Yes.
We need to know what she's thinking,
or she could betray us at any moment.
Why do I have to tell you?
I had to do it to protect myself!
Or I'd have been...
Is she trying to say it's self-defense?
Or could this all be an act?
It might hurt, but you're under
a lot of suspicion right now.
Unless you answer me,
I can't relax my guard around you.
All it takes is one hit from
behind, and it's over.
If you killed us,
you could get the eight chips you
need to escape this island.
I would never...
Sonar!
Is someone here?
Don't move.
It's still far away.
No one was seen, right?
Th-They found me...
I-I'll leave this place...
W-Wait.
But if I stay, they'll come here.
The killing will start again.
You should hide, too.
S-Sakamoto-han...
Wait.
They only found one person.
I'll act as a decoy and draw them off.
When I get back,
we'll finish our discussion.
What the hell am I doing?
When I played the game online,
I used to enjoy helping others like this.
But this time, I'm risking my life.
Time to get rid of them.
I'll run to the other side,
and I should appear to be
getting farther away.
If they're farther away in my next scan,
we won't have to fight.
I head into enemy territory to
recover a kidnapped girl.
Is there a reason to risk my life?
I saw it.
She's...
Episode 7: Virtual Bride
She's my...